(Bernadette:)-I love your shoes.
-Oh, thanks. They are cute, aren't they?
(Bernadette:)-Where'd you get them?
-Shoes for Less.
(Bernadette:)-I've been meaning to go over there.
-Oh, great selection, great prices.
(Sheldon:)My mother was right. Hell is real.
(Howard:)Come on, Sheldon,
let the women-folk chat.
(Penny:)Women-folk?
(Howard:)Gals? Chicks?
(Howard:)Utero-Americans?
(Penny:)-Just eat your dinner.
-Don't take him too seriously.
(Bernadette:)A lot of what he says
is intended as humor.
(Penny:)Yeah, well,
I don't think it's very funny.
(Bernadette:)Me neither,
but he just lights up when I laugh.
(Penny:)Howard, never let her go.
(Bernadette:)Leonard, Howard says you're working on
fundamental tests...
(Bernadette:)-...of quantum mechanics.
-I am. Are you interested in physics?
(Bernadette:)I find it fascinating.
(Bernadette:)If I hadn't gone into microbiology...